"""
    Questions data taken from: https://opentdb.com/
"""

question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In 'Mario Kart 64', Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In 'Sonic Adventure', you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
    "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'S.T.A.L.K.E.R.' series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  'the Zone'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Resident Evil 7' is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
